Sergey Nechepurenko

C++ developer

Email: sergnech.sw@gmail.com	Place of residence: Israel
Phone: +972533586061	https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergey-nech/

SUMMARY

I have excellent programming experience, knowledge of data structures and algorithms. I have good experience in analyzing business processes and designing an optimal data structure. I have developed databases and real-time TCP/IP network applications. I have a great desire to work intensively in order to be useful in the company and improve my skills.

SKILLS

- C++
- Go lang
- JavaScript
- HTML / CSS
- PHP

- Git
- Docker
- SQL (MySQL, FireBird)
- Linux
- NGINX, Apache, Iptables

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

C++ programmer

«Aral Plus», Moscow

2010-2022

- Developing software for accounting goods in the warehouse. Using C++, FireBird.
- Development of a program for tracking the working time of employees. Using C++,
 FireBird.
- Creation of a company website using PHP
- Developing web server log analyzer to protect the site from DDoS attacks. Using C++
- Written chat for site. The server part is written in C++ for Linux, the client part in JavaScript.

C++ and JavaScript programmer

«7th continent» Moscow

2000 -2010

- Cash register programming in C++
- Creation of a data analysis programs for the company's management. Using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MS SQL.
- Designing SQL databases on MS SQL, developing stored procedures.

C++ programmer

«Borovichi Refractories Plant» Russia

1999 - 2000

Developing warehouse programs using MS SQL and Delphi

EDUCATION

Software engineer. Novgorod State University. 1992-1997

LANGUAGES

English, Russian (native), Hebrew (basic)

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

I love learning new programming languages and new interesting information technologies. I love learning English. I love studying mathematics. In mathematics, I have done a lot of research on complex numbers and the Riemann zeta function. I wrote a program to plot mathematical functions. https://sergsergnn.github.io/gr/graph-js.htm